Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1950-2017
  - Articles and Chapters, 1950-2017 and undated; 1
    - Competitive Effects of Line-of-business Restrictions in Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Competitive Stability Under Weak Gross Substitutability: Nonlinear Price Adjustment and Adaptive Expectations, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Competitive Stability Under Weak Gross Substitutability: The `Euclidean Distance' Approach, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Conflict of Values: A Decision View, 2014 (Box 30)
    - Constraint Qualifications in Maximization Problems, 1961 (Box 30)
    - Consumption Leisure, 2009 (Box 30)
      Copy of article "Conspicuous Consumption, Inconspicuous Leisure" co-authored with Partha Dasgupta
    - Contingent Valuation of Non-use Values, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Contributions to Competition and Cooperation: Conversations with Nobelists about Economics and Political Science, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Control in Large Organizations, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box 30)
      Copy of published address to Institute of Management Sciences, includes Japanese translation
    - Cost- and Demand-theoretical Approaches to the Theory of Price Discrimination, 1973 (Box 30)
      Reprint, German translation
    - Cowles in the History of Economic Thought, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Criteria for Social Investment, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Criteria, Institutions, and Functions in Urban Development Decisions, 1970 (Box 30)
    - Current Developments in the Theory of Social Choice, 1977 (Box 30)
    - Dantzig and Economics, 2008 (Box 30)
      Reprint of article "George Dantzig in the development of economic analysis"
    - Decentralization and Computation in Resource Allocation, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Decision Theory and Operations Research, 1957 (Box 30)
    - Decision Theory and the Choice of a Level of Significance for the t-Test, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Decision-making Frameworks for Addressing Climate Change, 1996 (Box 30)
    - Demand for Information and the Distribution of Income, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 30)
      Reprint, copy, notes, drafts, related correspondence
    - Determination of Many-Commodity Preferences Scales by Two-Commodity Comparisons, 1952 (Box 30)
    - Difficulty in the Concept of Social Welfare, 1950 (Box 30)
    - Discounting and Public Investment Criteria, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Discounting, Morality and Gaming, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Distributed Information and the Role of the State in the Economy, 2002 (Box 30)
    - Division of Labor in the Economy, the Polity and Society, undated (Box 40)
    - Does a Good Place Value News?, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Dummett Review, 1997 (Box 30)
      Proof, related correspondence
    - Dussenberry's The Portfolio Approach, 1963 (Box 30)
      Copy of comment on "The Portfolio Approach to the Demand for Money and Other Assets" by Dussenberry
    - Dynamic Shortages and Price Rises: The Engineer-Scientist Case, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Dynamics of Technological Change, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Econ(nomics/logy), 2007 (Box 30)
    - Economic Aspects of Environmental Challenges, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Economic Aspects of Military Research and Development, 1955 (Box 30)
      Copy of draft
    - Economic Costs to Western Europe, 1963 (Box 30)
      Copy of article "The Economic Cost to Western Europe of Restricted Availability of Oil Imports"
    - Economic Development: The Present State of the Art, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Economic Dimensions of Occupational Segregation, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Economic Equilibrium, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Economic Growth, Carrying Capacity, and the Environment, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Economic History: A Necessary Though Not Sufficient Condition for an Economist, 1985 (Box 30)
    - Economic Implications of Learning By Doing, 1967 (Box 30)
    - Economic Integration and the Future of the Welfare State, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Economic Theory and the Financial Crisis, 2012 (Box 30)
      Copy, draft
    - Economic Transition: Speed and Scope, 2000 (Box 30)
    - Economic Welfare and the Allocation of Resources for Invention, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Economics and Inequality, 2011 (Box 30)
    - Economics as It is and as It is Developing, 1995 (Box 30)
    - Economics of 1984, 1983 (Box 40)
    - Economics of Agency, 1985 (Box 30)
    - Economics of Globalization, 2005 (Box 30)
      Copy of book foreword "Globalisation and Its Implications for International Security"
    - Economics of Information, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Economics of Information: Survey, 1996 (Box 30)
    - Economics of Moral Hazard, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Economists and Glory, 2009 (Box 30)
    - Economists' Voice, 2007 (Box 30)
      Copy of paper titled "Global Climate Change: A Challenge to Policy"
    - Edgeworths Ethick, 1994; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Original in German, drafts in English, and related correspondence
    - Education Department, 1995-1996 (Box 40)
      Draft of "Social Benefits of Education"
    - Edwin Mansfield Bio, 1999 (Box 31)
      Proofs, draft
    - Effects of the Price System and Market on Urban Economic Development, 1970; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Reprint, collected volume
    - Ehrlich Comment, 2002 (Box 31)
      Proofs, draft, related correspondence
    - Elements of the Economics of Information, 1996 (Box 31)
      Contains published lectures on economics of information and "Information and Increasing Returns"
    - Eminent Economists, 1991 (Box 31)
      Reprint of autobiographical contribution to Eminent Economists volume
    - Energy, 1972-1979 (Box 40)
      Drafts of "Redistributive Aspects of High and Rising Energy Prices"
    - Energy: The Short View of the Long, 1985 (Box 40)
    - Entry, Productivity, and Investment, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Environment and the Anthropocene Era, 2012 (Box 40)
    - Environmental Preservation, Uncertainty, and Irreversibility, 1974 (Box 31)
    - Equilibrium in Economics, 1987-1990 (Box 40)
      Copy, drafts
    - Evaluating Projects and Assessing Sustainable Development in Imperfect Economies, 2003 (Box 31)
    - Example of Dynamic Control of Negative Stock Externalities, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Excellence and Equity in Higher Education, 1993; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Reprint, drafts
    - Existence of an Equilibrium for a Competitive Economy, 1954 (Box 31)
    - Exposition of the Theory of Choice Under Uncertainty, 1992 (Box 31)
    - Extended Sympathy and the Possibility of Social Choice, 1978 (Box 31)
      Includes reprint and draft
    - Extension of the Basic Theorems of Classical Welfare Economics, 1952 (Box 31)
    - External Costs of Voting Rules, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Firms in General Equilibrium Theory, 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Foreword to Privatisation, Conversion and Enterprise Reform in Russia, 1995 (Box 31)
      Foreword to edited volume by McFaul and Perlmutter
    - Foreword to Samuelsonian Economics and the 21st Century, 2006 (Box 31)
      Proofs and some limited correspondence
    - Foreword to Valuing Environmental Preferences, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Formal Theories of Social Welfare, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Freedom and Social Choice, 2006 (Box 31)
    - Functions of a Theory of Behavior Under Uncertainty, 1959 (Box 31)
    - Functions of Social Choice Theory, 1997 (Box 31)
      Copy, includes Introduction to collected volume
    - Future and the Present in Economic Life, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Futures Markets: Some Theoretical Perspectives, 1981 (Box 31)
    - General Economic Equilibrium, 1973 (Box 31)
    - General Economic Equilibrium: Purpose, Analytic Techniques, Collective Choice, 1972-1973; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Book of Nobel speeches for 1972, drafts
    - General Economic Theory and Income Distribution, 1994 (Box 31)
    - General Economic Theory and the Emergence of Theories of Economic Development, 1988 (Box 31)
    - General Resilience, 2012 (Box 31)
    - General Saddle Point Results for Constrained Optimization, 1971 (Box 31)
      Draft, reprint
    - Genesis of Dynamic Systems Governed by Metzler Matrics, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Genesis of Optimal Inventory Policy, 2002; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Copy, includes 50th anniversary issue
    - Genetic Diversity, 2004 (Box 31)
    - Genuine Savings and Population, 2003-2009; 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Gifts and Exchanges, 1972-1981; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Draft, reprint, multiple copies
    - Girshik, Meyer A., 1970 (Box 31)
    - Gospel According to Mr. and Mrs. Friedman, 1980 (Box 31)
      Original, copy
    - Government Decision Making and the Preciousness of Human Life, 1974 (Box 31)
    - Government Regulation: Pluses and Minuses, 1981 (Box 31)
    - Gradient Methods for Constrained Maximia, 1957 (Box 31)
    - Guttman Comment, 1998 (Box 31)
      Draft, related correspondence
    - Harsanyi, John C., 2001 (Box 31)
    - Health and Society, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Health Care Reform, 2009 (Box 31)
    - Herbert Scarf's Contributions to Economics, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Reprint, drafts, related correspondence
    - Hicks Notice, 1994-2009 (Box 40)
      Drafts of "Capital Theory as an Extension of Value Theory" in honor of John Hicks, includes related correspondence and notes
    - Higher Education as a Filter, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Homogeneous Systems in Mathematical Economics, 1950 (Box 31)
    - Hotelling Memoir, 2005 (Box 31)
    - How Growth can Undermine Growth, 2011 (Box 31)
      Copy, proofs
    - How Should Benefits and Costs be Discounted in an Intergenerational Context, 2012 (Box 31)
    - Impact of Operations Research and Decision Theory on Teaching and Research in Microeconomics, 1996 (Box 31)
    - Import Substitution in Leontief Models, 1954 (Box 31)
    - In Memoriam: John C. Harsanyi, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Income Testing and Social Welfare, undated (Box 40)
    - Increasing Income Inequality, undated (Box 40)
    - Increasing Returns: Historical Issues and Path Dependence, 2000; 2 folders (Box 31)
      Reprint, copy, draft, and related correspondence
    - Inequalities in Income and Wealth, 1996 (Box 31)
    - Information Acquisition and the Resolution of Conflict, 1995 (Box 31)
    - Information and Economic Behavior, 1973 (Box 31)
      Reprint, draft
    - Information and Innovation Diffusion, 2017 (Box 40)
    - Information and the Organization of Industry, 1994; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Information, Responsibility, and Human Services, 1990 (Box 31)
    - Informational Equivalence of Signals, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Informational Structure of the Firm, 1985 (Box 31)
    - Innovation and Increasing Returns to Scale, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Innovation in Large and Small Firms, 1983; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Insurance, risk and allocation of production factors, 1964 (Box 31)
      Reprint of Dutch Translation
    - Intergenerational Equity, 1999 (Box 31)
    - International Peace-Keeping Forces: Economics and Politics, 1994 (Box 31)
    - Intertemporal Equity, 1996 (Box 31)
    - Interview with Kenneth Arrow by J. Kelly, 1986 (Box 40)
    - Introductory Remarks on the History of Game Theory, 2003 (Box 31)
    - Invaluable Goods, 1997 (Box 31)
    - Is the World Going Socialist, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Is there a Role for Benefit-Cost Analysis in Environmental, Health, and Safety Regulation?, 1996 (Box 31)
    - JEP Discrimination, 1998 (Box 40)
      Drafts of "What Has Economics to Say About Discrimination", related correspondence
    - Joan Robinson and Modern Economic Theory: An Interview, 1989 (Box 31)
    - John Holland and the Evolution of Economics, 2005 (Box 31)
    - Kapitaltheorie als Erweiterung der Werttheorie, 1997 (Box 31)
      Original in German
    - Knowledge as a Factor of Production, 2000 (Box 31)
    - Knowledge, Belief and the Economic System, 2013 (Box 31)
    - Levin Paper, 2007-2009 (Box 40)
      Draft and reprint of "Intergenerational resource transfers with random offspring numbers"
    - Liberman - Intro A, 1994-1995; 5 files derived from floppy disk; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes draft writing.
    - Limitations of the Profit Motive, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Limited Knowledge and Economic Analysis, 1974 (Box 31)
    - Limits of the Market in Resource Allocation, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Little's Critique of Welfare Economics, 1951 (Box 31)
    - Locus of Decisions about AIDS/HIV, Malaria Treatment: what does Welfare Economics Say?, 2004 (Box 31)
    - Looming Global-Scale Failures and Missing Institutions, 2009 (Box 31)
    - Major Developments in Economics, 2000-2001 (Box 40)
    - Malaria, 2005 (Box 31)
    - Marschak, Jacob, 1978; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Reprint, copy, drafts, and related correspondence
    - Marschak's Contributions to the Economics of Decision and Information, 1981; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Reprint, related correspondence and notes
    - Mathematical Models in the Social Sciences, 1951 (Box 32)
      Copy, French translation
    - Measurement of Price Changes, 1958 (Box 32)
    - Measurement of Real Value Added, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Methodological Individualism and Social Knowledge, 1994 (Box 32)
    - Microeconomic Simulation, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Microeconomics and Operations Research, 2015 (Box 32)
    - Models of Job Discrimination, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Neoclassical Theory and Its Discontents, 1993-1994 (Box 40)
    - New Antimalarial Drugs, 2004 (Box 32)
    - New Ideas in Economic Theory, 1970 (Box 32)
    - New Palgrave, 1981-1992; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Nikkei Op-Ed, 1997 (Box 39)
      Draft of "What was the Twentieth Century"
    - Nonlinear Pricing in Monopoly and Oligopoly, 1998 (Box 39)
    - Note on Dynamic Stability, 1957 (Box 32)
    - Note on Expectations and Stability, 1957 (Box 32)
      Draft, copy
    - Note on Expectations Equilibrium in Bayesian Settings, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Note on the Rand Preference Experiments, 1952 (Box 32)
    - Note on Uncertainty and Discounting in Models of Economic Growth, 2009 (Box 32)
    - Notes on Sequence Economies, Transactions Costs, and Uncertainty, 1999 (Box 32)
    - Nozick's Entitlement Theory of Justice, 1978 (Box 32)
    - Olson Review, 2000 (Box 32)
      Original, proofs, draft
    - On a Theorem of Arrow: Comment, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - On Partitioning a Sample with Binary-type Questions in Lieu of Collecting Observations, 1981 (Box 32)
    - On the Agenda of Organization, 1974 (Box 32)
    - On the Stability of the Competitive Equilibrium, 1957 (Box 32)
    - On the Stability of the Competitive Equilibrium, II, 1959 (Box 32)
    - On the Use of Winds in Flight Planning, 1949 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Advertising Policy Under Dynamic Conditions, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Allocation of Risk-bearing, 1963-1964 (Box 32)
    - Optimal and Voluntary Income Distribution, 1981 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Capital Adjustment, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Capital Policy, the Cost of Capital, and Myopic Decision Rules, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Consumer Allocation over an Infinite Horizon, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Growth with Irreversible Investments, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Insurance and Generalized Deductibles, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Inventory Policy, 1951 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Pricing and Natural Resources, 1980 (Box 39)
    - Optimal Pricing, use and Exploration of Uncertain Natural Resource Stocks, 1978-1982 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Public Investment Policy and Controllability with Fixed Private Savings Ratio, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Optimal Savings and Population, 2007 (Box 32)
    - Optimality Condition for Decision-making Under Ignorance, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Origins of the Impossibility Theorem, 1991; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Copy, related correspondence
    - Overview of the Conference, in "International Finance and Trade", 1988 (Box 32)
    - Pareto Efficiency with Costly Transfers, 1981; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Reprint, includes book chapter version
    - Path Dependence and Competitive Equilibrium, 2004 (Box 32)
    - Peace Economics, Peace Science, and Public Policy, 1995 (Box 32)
    - Permanent and Transitory Substitution Effects in Health Insurance Experiments, 1984 (Box 32)
    - Personal Agenda for the Next Decade, 2004 (Box 32)
    - Petroleum Price Regulation, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Place of Institutions in the Economy, 1998 (Box 32)
    - Place of Moral Obligation in Preference Systems, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Planning and Uncertainty, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Political and Economic Evaluation of Social Effects and Externalities, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Population, Development and Human Nature, 2002 (Box 32)
    - Price-Quantity Adjustments in Multiple Markets with Rising Demands, 1959 (Box 32)
    - Principe de Rationalité dan les Décisions Collectives, 1952 (Box 32)
      Reprint of French translation
    - Problems of Resource Allocation in US Medical Care, 1972; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Production and Distribution of Knowledge, 1994 (Box 32)
    - Production Function for the Repairman Problem, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Promise of Prediction Markets, 2008 (Box 32)
    - Property Rights Doctrine and Demand Revelation under Incomplete Information, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Proposed Reforms of the Economic System in the USSE, 1990 (Box 39)
    - Quantity Adjustments in Resource Allocation: A Statistical Interpretation, 1976 (Box 32)
    - Quasi-Concave Programming, 1961 (Box 32)
    - Radin Review, 1997 (Box 32)
    - Rate of Discount for Long-Term Public Investment, 1976 (Box 32)
    - Rate of Discount on Public Investment with Imperfect Capital Markets, 1982 (Box 32)
    - Rational Choice and Humanities, 2006 (Box 39)
    - Rational Choice Functions and Orderings, 1959 (Box 32)
      Draft, French translation
    - Rationality of Self and Others, 1986; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Rawls's Principle of Just Saving, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Real and Nominal Magnitudes in Economics, 1980-1981; 3 folders (Box 32)
      Reprint, original, multiple copies
    - Reduction of Constrained Maxima to Saddle-Point Problems, 1954-1955 (Box 32)
    - Reflections on Political Science, 1999 (Box 32)
    - Reflections on the Reflections, 2001 (Box 32)
    - Regulation, 1981 (Box 32)
    - Remarks on Utility and Game Theory, 1950 (Box 32)
    - Research in Management Controls, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Returns to Investing in Health, 2013 (Box 39)
    - Returns to Scale, Information, and Economic Growth, 1991 (Box 39)
    - Review of Dangerous Currents, Thurow, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Review of Free to Choose, Friedman, 1980 (Box 32)
      Copy and draft
    - Review of Poverty and Famines, Sen, 1982 (Box 32)
    - Ricardo's Work as Viewed by Later Economists, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 32)
      Reprint, draft, includes German translation and related correspondence
    - Risk Allocation and Information: Some Recent Theoretical Development, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Risk Perception in Psychology and Economics, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Role of Securities in the Optimal Allocation of Risk Bearing, 1953 (Box 40)
    - Rothschild Paper, 1973 (Box 39)
      Draft of "Preliminary Notes on Equilibrium Price Distributions with Limited Information", includes notes
    - Samuelson Collected, 1967 (Box 40)
    - Sex Differentiation in Annuities, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Skalenertragselebatte im Economic Journal zwischen 1922 und 1930, 2001 (Box 40)
    - Social Choice Perspective, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Social Discount Rate, 1969 (Box 40)
    - Social Responsibility and Economic Efficiency, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Social-Ecological Systems as Complex Adaptive Systems: Modeling and Policy Implications, 2012 (Box 40)
    - Some Developments in Economic Theory Since 1940: An Eyewitness Account, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Some Ordinalist Utilitarian Notes on Rawls's Theory of Justice, 1977 (Box 40)
      Italian translation
    - Some Remarks on the Equilibria of Economic Systems, 1960 (Box 40)
    - Some Tests of the International Comparisons of Factor Efficiency with the CES Production Function. A Reply, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Speed and Scope of Transition, 1997 (Box 40)
    - Stability Independent of Adjustment Speed, 1974 (Box 40)
    - Stability of the Gradient Process in n-Person Games, 1960 (Box 40)
    - Statistical Requirements for Greek Economic Planning, 1965 (Box 40)
    - Statistics and Economic Policy, 1957 (Box 40)
      Reprint, French translation, German translation
    - Subject Matter of Social Choice Theory, 2001 (Box 39)
      Draft, includes notes
    - Sustainability and Measurement of Wealth, 2012 (Box 39)
    - Team Theory and Decentralized Resource Allocation: An Example, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Team Theory and Distributed Processing: Surprise Attack, 1999 (Box 40)
    - Technical Information and Industrial Structure, 1996 (Box 40)
    - Technical Information, Returns to Scale, and the Existence of Competitive Equilibrium, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Theorem on Expectations and the Stability of Equilibrium, 1956 (Box 40)
    - Theoretical Issues in Health Insurance, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Theory of Discrimination, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Theory of Justice by John Rawls: Two Review Articles, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Theory of Risk-Bearing: Small and Great Risks, 1996 (Box 40)
    - Thorstein Veblen as an Economic Theorist, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Tinbergen on Economic Policy, 1958 (Box 40)
    - Toward a 21st Century Health Care System, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Trade-Off Between Growth and Equity, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Transition from Communism to an Alternative Economic Organisation, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Transition from Socialism, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Tullock and an Existence Theorem, 1969 (Box 40)
    - Two Cheers for Government Regulation, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Uncertainty and Discounting in Models of Economic Growth, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Uncertainty and the Evaluation of Public Investment Decisions, 1970 (Box 40)
    - Uncertainty and the Value of Public Investment, undated (Box 39)
    - Uncertainty and the Welfare Economics of Medical Care, 1963-1996; 2 folders (Box 40)
      Reprint, includes Comment and Reply and French translation
    - Uniqueness of the Internal Rate of Return with Variable Life Investment, 1969 (Box 40)
    - Use of Genetics and Other Medical Information: Ethical and Market Dilemmas, 1995 (Box 40)
    - Utilitarian Approach to the Concept of Equality in Public Expenditures, 1971 (Box 40)
    - Utilities, Attitudes, Choices: A Review Note, 1958 (Box 40)
    - Utility and Expectation in Economic Behavior, 1963 (Box 40)
    - Value of and Demand for Information, 1972 (Box 40)
    - Values and Collective Decision-making, 1967 (Box 40)
    - Vertical Integration and Communication, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Viability and Equity of Capitalism, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Von Neumann and the Existence Theorem for General Equilibrium, 1989 (Box 40)
    - Welfare Analysis of Changes in Health Coinsurance Rates, 1976 (Box 40)
    - What Has Economics to Say About Racial Discrimination, 1998 (Box 40)
    - Wingspread, 1982 (Box 40)
      Copy of "Planning and Uncertainty" contribution to collected volume
    - Winter on Schumpeter, 2006 (Box 40)
    - Work of Ragnar Frisch, Econometrician, 1960 (Box 40)
  - Books, 1958-2017; 2
    Contains copies of books authored and edited by Arrow. In some cases there are copies of multiple editions of books and copies of translations.
    - Applied Research for Social Policy, 1979 (Box 33)
      Abt Books
    - Balance between Industry and Agriculture in Economic Development, 1988 (Box 33)
      Macmillan Press
    - Barriers to Conflict Resolution, 1995 (Box 33)
      W.W. Norton and Company
    - Books electronic records, 2010-2014; 23 files; 44 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Collected Papers of Kenneth Arrow, 1979-1985; 3 folders (Box 39)
      Drafts, notes, and correspondence related to collected papers book series
    - Collected Papers of Kenneth J. Arrow: Volume 6, Applied Economics, 1985 (Box 33)
      Belknap Press of Harvard University Press
    - Collected Papers of Kenneth J. Arrow: Volume 4, Economics of Information (Chinese), 1989 (Box 33)